<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to Shaderwit.ch on Shaderwit.ch - Unreal Engine render pipeline documentation and tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to Shaderwit.ch on Shaderwit.ch - Unreal Engine render pipeline documentation and tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:37:22 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/index.html</guid>
      <description>Shaderwit.ch is a place for tutorials I have created on the topic of that spooky thing the Unreal Engine community hasdeemed Shader Witchcraft, &#34;Black Magic&#34;, or that seemingly incredibly difficult mathematics topic to render graphicsthat everyone wants to learn, but no one wants to touch - I hope to make this easier for you.The secondary long-term goal of this is to also document the even harder to understand render pipeline of Unreal Engine,and to give a cursory overview of where Unreal sets up things like Shading Models, Render calls, and those hundredsof .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shader Witchcraft</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/shaderwitchcraft/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/shaderwitchcraft/index.html</guid>
      <description>Shader Witch [ shay-der wich ]noun
A mysterious being that practices the dark arts of manipulating pixels, creating shaders and manifesting chaos in a given renderer. My little playground of tutorials on teaching you Shader Witchcraft, the art of shader black magic, mathematics and a smidge of graphics programming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Render Pipeline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/unrealrenderpipeline/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:37:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/unrealrenderpipeline/index.html</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this section of Shaderwit.ch is to give an overview and to document areas of Unreal Engine&amp;rsquo;s render pipeline that I have explored. Unfortunately, most things found here - with the exception of anything under Plugins - will require that you run a custom build of the engine since this will require engine modification to proceed.
To learn to build your own version of Unreal Engine please see the official documentation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Website Status</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/website/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/website/index.html</guid>
      <description>Here you can find a list of all the current articles that are currently being worked on, and if they are being planned or Work in Progress.
PageAuthorStatusGetting StartedAlessa &amp;#34;Codekitten&amp;#34; BakerWork in ProgressCreating a Shading ModelAlessa &amp;#34;Codekitten&amp;#34; BakerWork in ProgressScene View ExtensionsAlessa &amp;#34;Codekitten&amp;#34; BakerWork in Progress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/authors/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/authors/index.html</guid>
      <description>As this website progresses, I hope to have multiple contributors who can share their knowledge and expertise on rendering and developing shaders in Unreal Engine. Here you will find the list of contributors to the website, along with their socials, and a list of articles they have written or helped write.
Should you wish to contribute, you can message me on Discord (Codekitten) or email me at Alessa@codekitten.me.
Alessa ❤️</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>